kara no kokoro wo terasu mono wa nani?
What brightens up an empty heart?
sakebi tsuzukeru hikari todoku made
I will keep on singing until the light reaches you
falling through the cracks kurayami e ochiteku
Falling through the cracks, Falling into the darkness
anata no sono te o zettai hanasanai
I will never let go of your hand
tell me the story of your life mada michi no tochuu
Tell me the story of your life, We're still on our way
anata o watashi wa zettai akiramenai
I will never give up on you
osaerarenai shoudou nanigenai hibi wa aijyou
Urges I can't suppress, I live for the ordinary days
natsukashii kaze ni furimukeba itsud
When I turn my cheek to a nostalgic wind
emo anata no koe ga suru yo
I always hear your voice
underdog wa wander around
Underdog will Wander around
mawari michi shitemo nigeru yori mashi yo
Even if I take the long way around,
it's better than running away
jibun de jibun o shinjirare nakucha dare wo shinjiru no?
If I can't learn to believe in myself,
then who can I believe in?
hikari ni sono te kazase
Hold up your hand to the light
shining through the clouds kurayami e ochiteku
Shining through the clouds, Falling into the darkness
anata no sono te o zettai hanasanai
I will never let go of your hand
tell me what is on your mind hateshinai yume wo
Tell me what is on your mind,
Chasing the never ending dream
oikake bokura wa zettai akiramenai
We will never give up
kotae no nai jinsei ni kujike sou ni naru kedo
Discouraged by a life without answers, but I...
don’t give it up! keep it up! turn it upside down!
Don't give it up! Keep it up! Turn it upside down!
kokoro wa tsunagatteru yo tatoe tooku hanaretemo
Our hearts will always be connected,
no matter how far apart we may be
tomo ni tomo ni ikiteyukou
Let's share this life together
I won't let you get away... Gengo!
Dawn
《シカマル : 逃がさねえぞ ゲンゴ！》
To think, Shikamaru had
this many reinforcements
waiting in the wings.
(サイ)シカマルが これだけの援軍を
待機させていたとはね。
As expected of a coward like him.
I think you're misunderstanding something,
so I'm going to set you right.
臆病な彼には
お似合いってことかな。
We barged in on our own.
(テマリ)勘違いしているようだから
教えてやるが→
私らは勝手におしかけただけだ。
Shikamaru is hiding something.
Yes.
((シカマルは何かを隠している。
It must be serious,
for him to act alone.
(我愛羅)ああ あいつが
独自に動くからには→
Will you look into it, Temari?
よほどの事情があるはずだ。
Use as much manpower as necessary.
調べてくれるか テマリ？
Are you sure?
必要なら 人手は
いくらでも使っていい。
Shikamaru is a Leaf shinobi.
いいのか？
シカマルは 木ノ葉の忍だぞ。
Sand or Leaf... The age of
drawing lines is over.
砂だ 木ノ葉だという時代は
終わったんだ。
A man who is essential to
the Alliance is worth it.
連合に必要な男のためなら
惜しくはない。
Besides...
I doubt the Hokage would
willingly give us intel.
もっとも あの火影が→
I'll drag it out of him.
素直に情報を渡すとは
思えないが。
I know you understand,
but do it as peacefully as possible.
聞き出すさ。
わかっているだろうが
できるだけ平和的にだぞ。
Sure, I'll do it as peacefully...
ああ 平和的にやるさ
できるだけね。
as I can.
And...?
Is there something else
you needed to ask me?
(カカシ)それで
これ以上 何が聞きたいの？
Shikamaru is now...
(シカマルは 今…))
Anyway, we rushed over
after hearing that
Shikamaru was in trouble.
(チョウジ)それで
シカマルのピンチを知った僕らは➡
Out of friendship, right?
飛んできたってわけ。
That brings a tear to my eye.
Well, wait.
友情ってやつかい？
泣かせるね。
I'll make you cry so hard,
you'll hate it.
待ってろ 今から
嫌というほど泣かせてやる。
Leave Sai to me.
He's strong, you know.
Yeah, I know.
(いの)サイは私に任せて。
あいつは強いぞ。
うん 知ってる。
Sorry, Ino,
but you're no match for me.
悪いけど キミでは
相手にならないよ いの。
Let me take the old man!
Oh?
あのおじさんは僕が。
(朧)ほう。
Wind Scythe Jutsu!
カマイタチの術！
どりゃ～！
Wow, that was a surprise.
But you won't get me
a second time!
へえ 驚いた
でも２度目はない。
I shall show no mercy,
even if you are just a brat!
Expansion Jutsu!
小童が相手でも
容赦はしないでござる。
What?!
(チョウジ)倍化の術！
なんと！
Who did you just call a brat?
誰が小童だって？
Your name is Soku, right?
You should be supporting Shikamaru.
鏃とかいったか
シカマルの隣にいるべきお前が→
So, what the hell are you doing?!
Like, I simply chose my master
いったいなんだ
そのざまは？
in order to realize
my full potential.
(鏃)私はただ この力を
活かせる主を選んだだけだし。
What?
Like, staying under
a weakling like Shikamaru
なんだと？
is too tedious and futile!
シカマルみたいな
弱っちいやつの下にいたら→
窮屈でしかたないって意味だし！
Damn!
Aim more carefully next time.
チッ！
今度は もっとよく狙うんだな。
If you miss again...
you'll lose.
次に外せば お前の負けだ。
You will definitely
accept my will, Shikamaru.
(ゲンゴ)貴君は必ず 私の志を
受け入れることになるのだよ。
Your head's nothing
but a flower garden!
シカマル君。
てめえの頭は
どこまでも お花畑だな！
Resign yourself...
It's all too late.
(ゲンゴ)諦めたまえ。
すでに手遅れなのだ。
Too late?
What the hell do you mean?!
手遅れだと？
いったい どういう意味だ？
Not bad!
But if you're already out of breath
against one opponent,
やるじゃないか。
でも 一頭を相手に
その息の上がりようじゃ→
you don't have a chance.
Sai, wake up!
話にならないね。
Why don't you worry
about yourself instead of me?
サイ 目を覚まして！
"I don't even know myself anymore..."
僕より
自分の心配をしたらどうだい？
That's what you supposedly wrote
in the last missive you sent.
「自分がわからない」。
あんたが
最後に送ってよこした文に→
I have the will that Lord Gengo
bestowed upon me.
そう書いてあったそうよ。
僕には ゲンゴ様からいただいた
志がある。
So... I'm not lost anymore!
だから もう
迷いなんかない。
Oh...
Did I overdo it?
あれ？ やりすぎちゃったかな？
His chakra's not reacting...
チャクラの反応がない。
No way... Did he die?
まさか死んじゃったんじゃ…。
You could say that making my target
misread chakra is my specialty.
うぐっ！
対象となる相手に
チャクラの錯誤をもたらすのは→
I have no idea what you're saying...
拙者の得意とするところでござる。
何言ってるか… さっぱりだ。
Shikamaru should be kneeling
before Lord Gengo about now.
シカマルも今頃 ゲンゴ様の前で
ひざまずいているでござるよ。
Shikamaru would never...
シカマルが 屈したり…。
What brute strength!
... bow down to anyone!
なんという馬鹿力!?
するもんか～！
Partial Expansion Jutsu!
Why you—!
部分倍化の術。
おのれ…。
ぐわっ！
Take this!
くらえ！
チッ！
Cyclone Scythe Jutsu!
くっ…。
大カマイタチの術！
ハァ ハァ ハァ ハァ ハァ…。
I'll never give up...
on a precious friend!
大切な仲間のために
私は絶対 諦めない。
Around now, your precious friend
should be receiving Lord Gengo's will.
その大切なシカマルは→
今頃 ゲンゴ様に
志をいただいているはずさ。
Even as you lay your life on the line.
You don't understand, do you?
キミが
いくら命を張ったところでね。
The precious friend I'm talking about...
なんにも わかってないのね。
is you!
大切な仲間ってのはさ→
You belong to the Hidden Leaf.
あんたのことよ！
Don't ever forget that!
((お前は 木ノ葉の一員だ。
それを忘れんな！))
Being friends is useless!
Then...
友達ごっこなんて くだらないね。
Then what's that on your cheek?
だったら
あんたの頬をつたっている→
それは何？
Mind Transmission Jutsu!
心転身の術！
Let me take over your mind
for a little while.
しばらく あんたの精神を
乗っ取らせてもらうわ。
I didn't lure you in here
just to prevent you from
using your shadows.
(ゲンゴ)
貴君を ここへ誘い込んだのは→
When a human loses
the ability to see and smell,
影を使わせないためだけではない。
his sense of hearing
becomes much sharper.
視覚や嗅覚を奪われれば→
Giving you an even
greater advantage, huh?
人間は
それだけ聴覚が鋭敏になる。
ますます
てめえに有利ってわけか。
In the shinobi world,
you're either the user or the used.
(ゲンゴ)忍の世界には➡
利用する人間と される人間の
どちらかしかいない。
What're you talking about?
Words from a shinobi that
I once believed in...
何の話だ？
(ゲンゴ)
私が かつて信じた忍の言葉だよ。
Surely, even you've heard
the name Zabuza Momochi.
貴君も
桃地再不斬という名くらいは➡
Zabuza...
聞いたことがあるだろう。
Wasn't he the instigator of
the Mizukage assassination incident?
(シカマル)再不斬… たしか→
水影暗殺事件を
起こしたとかっていう…。
After the failed coup d'état,
we deserted the village.
(ゲンゴ)クーデター未遂ののち
私たちは里を抜けた。
We had faith in Zabuza's promise
to return some day to create
the ideal society.
いつか舞い戻り
理想の社会を作るという→
But the hardships of wandering
took its toll and changed him.
再不斬の言葉を信じたのだ。
しかし 過酷な放浪は
彼を変えてしまった。
And so, I used Zabuza instead.
だから私は
逆に再不斬を利用したのさ。
Just as he had taught.
To put it bluntly,
you sold out your friend.
彼の教えどおりにね。
要は仲間を売ったって話だろ？
And I settled here with
my comrades.
(ゲンゴ)そして 同志とともに
私は この地に移った。
In order to create the ideal society
that Zabuza could not.
再不斬のなしえなかった
理想の社会を築くためにな。
And now, it's finally becoming a reality.
今ようやく
思いが実現しようとしている。
Don't you want to usher
in that moment with me?
貴君も ともに
その瞬間を迎えたくないかね？
No thanks!
The only society I'll sacrifice
my life to protect
ごめんだぜ。
is the Hidden Leaf!
The same way that your father
and mentor did?
俺が この身を捧げて守りたいのは
木ノ葉だ！
(ゲンゴ)お父上や恩師が
そうしたようにか？
You have no right to talk about
my dad or Asuma!
軽々しく 親父やアスマのことを
口にするんじゃねえ！
I'll tear down your ideals!
てめえの理想とやらは
俺が打ち砕いてやるぜ。
What has happened... to me?
拙者は 何を…。
You are...?
おぬしは…。
Like, my head is throbbing...
頭が ガンガンするし。
That guy's...
the only one left.
あとは あいつだけだな。
Sai... answer me!
((サイ 返事をして！ サイ！
Sai!
サイ…。
Who are you?
I'm your friend.
キミは誰？
No...
あんたの友達よ。
They are my only friends.
違う
僕の友達は この子たちだけだ。
That's just what that guy Gengo
made you believe!
ゲンゴってやつに
そう思い込まされているだけよ！
Don't come any closer! Go away!
来るな 向こうへ行け！
Let's go back together, Sai.
一緒に帰ろう サイ。
Everyone is waiting for you.
(みんなが
あんたのことを待ってる))
Sai... Sai!
サイ… サイ。
Ino?
You're back!
いの？
Where is Shikamaru?!
戻ったのね！
シカマルは？
Shikamaru went after that Gengo guy.
シカマルなら
ゲンゴってやつを追っていったわ。
That's not good!
I have to let Shikamaru
know right away!
ダメだ！ 今すぐ シカマルに伝えなきゃ。
No matter what happens...
He can't turn around!
何があっても
振り向いちゃいけない！
Is the Hidden Leaf
that important to you?
Damned right it is!
(ゲンゴ)それほどまでに
木ノ葉が大事か？
Then I'll let you in on something good...
あたりめえだ！
Do you think that I only isolated
myself in this region
(ゲンゴ)ならば もう一つ
いい話を聞かせよう。
and did nothing else?
私が この辺境の地にこもって
何もせず→
What would you think
座していただけだと思うかね？
if I've sent my initiates with
the will I bestowed upon them,
もし 志を授けた同志たちを→
into all of the Hidden Villages?
すでに 各国に
潜伏させているとしたら どうだ？
The people of the Five Great Nations
aren't blind.
Your people may have
infiltrated the core,
五大国の連中の目も節穴じゃねえ。
but they'll get caught in time.
いくら中枢部に
もぐり込ませようが→
I'm talking about the citizens...
The safety of those
who are most dear to you...
いずれは網に引っかかる。
(ゲンゴ)里の人々…
例えば キミのごく身近な人の→
What did you say?
安全のことを言っているのだ。
One signal from me,
and they will create an incident.
なん… だと？
私の合図ひとつで
彼らはいつでも事を起こせる。
You don't have the means to stop it.
貴君にそれを止めるすべはない。
You're bluffing!
In time, you'll see if I'm lying or not.
ブラフだ！
(ゲンゴ)ウソかまことかは 今にわかる。
Stop!
Don't you dare touch Mirai!
Big Brother Shika!
(紅)やめろ ミライに手を出すな！
Mirai!
Y-You can't fool me...
(ミライ)シカの兄ちゃ…。
(紅)ミライ ミライ！
ふ… 振り返ってたまるかよ。
I've already figured out that
you infuse chakra into your voice
てめえが声にチャクラを流し込み→
to manipulate people.
人を操ろうとしてることは
お見通しなんだ！
The more you resist with your mind,
the more the heart seeks it.
(ゲンゴ)頭で振り返るまいと
すればするほど→
心は逆を求めるものだ。
Big Brother Shika!
Mirai!
クッ…。
(ミライ)シカの兄ちゃ…。
You'll pay if you lay
a hand on Mirai...
(紅)ミライ！
I'll make sure your breath
is completely snuffed out.
ミライに手を出しやがったら
承知しねえ。
そんときは てめえの息の根も
止めてやる！
Kill... Kill...
– Gengo, you're dangerous.
– Kill... Kill...
殺せ 殺せ…。
(シカマル)ゲンゴ てめえは危険だ。
生かしちゃおけねえ。
I can't let you go on living.
This is to protect the Hidden Leaf!
– It's for that reason that...
– Kill... Kill...
木ノ葉を守るためだ。
I've come to carry out
a mission that's not like me!
そのために
らしくねえ役目まで負って➡
– In order to make Naruto the Hokage!
– Kill... Kill...
俺は ここに来たんだ！
ナルトを 火影にするために！
Naruto...
ナルト。
Ramen!
(ナルト)ラーメン。
Huh?
What the hell was that?
はぁ？ んだよ それ。
What's the matter, Shikamaru?
Now, confront the darkness
that consumes your heart!
(ゲンゴ)どうした シカマル？
さあ 己の心に巣食う闇と
向き合うのだ。
フッ。
I-I have to get it right
the next time.
俺 次こそ完璧に
こなさなきゃいけないんだ。
Look, you're just a brat,
so it's okay if you ease up a little.
あのな ガキなんだから
もうちょい気楽でいいんだよ。
But it's my fault that my friends...
でも 俺のせいで仲間が…。
Thinking about your friends
is important.
仲間を思う気持は大事だけどよ→
But you don't have to take on
all that responsibility.
そんなに全部を
しょい込むことはないんだぜ。
'Cuz it's a drag.
めんどくせぇからよ。
Why?
Why doesn't my jutsu work on you?
なぜだ？ なぜ術にかからない？
Your heart is full of cracks!
貴様の心は
隙だらけではないか！
Yeah... My heart is full of cracks...
そうさ 俺の心は隙だらけ。
In fact, it's nothing but one big crack.
いや 隙しかねえんだ。
I-Impossible!
Your words don't have
any effect on me anymore.
バ バカな！
てめえの言葉は
もう俺には効かねえ！
I finally understand.
Earlier, you said you came to
this land with your comrades.
ようやくわかったぜ。
But why isn't there a single comrade
standing beside you?
さっき同志と一緒に
この国に来たと言ったな？
だったら どうして
てめえの横には→
You probably killed them all,
and hid them in this castle, right?
誰ひとり いねえんだろうな？
そいつら全部葬っちまって
この城に隠したんだろ？
You're all alone,
because you only believe in
using others or being used.
他人を利用するか されるかでしか
考えられねえ てめえは孤独だ！
This place is like peering deep
into your heart!
ここは まるで てめえの心の奥を
のぞき見てるようだぜ。
You and I are alike!
We're smart, we can't trust anyone!
貴様と私は似ている！
Don't lump me in with you!
頭がキレるせいで
他人を信用できない。
一緒にすんじゃねえ！
You—!
Looks like you're still conscious!
貴様ら！
Yeah, but it was touch and
go for a little while.
まだ 正気のようだな。
Ro, Soku!
あぁ。 ちょっと危なかったけどな。
Let's go.
(シカマル)朧！ 鏃！
Okay, let's clean this up quickly!
いくぞ。
よし！ さっさと片づけちゃおう。
Why don't we leave it
to them this time?
Yeah, you're right...
今回は
あいつらに任せてみないか？
Shikamaru did just call
on those two.
そっか…
シカマルが認めた２人だもんね。
はぁ～っ！
A clone?!
That's right. With his chakra—!
分身か！
確かに やつのチャクラを…。
Enveloping his shadow
with chakra?!
Which one is real?
影に チャクラをまとわせるだと!?
どれが 実体だ？
I can't... move!
If you stop me,
the world of the shinobi will decline!
体が… 動かん！
私を止めれば
忍の世界は 必ず 衰退する！
Don't you care
if you're consigned
to a life of servitude under
the Feudal Lords?
大名に奉仕するだけの
卑しい存在に落ちぶれても→
A place where even the easygoing
can live in their own way...
かまわぬと いうのか!?
ぼんやり生きたいやつらでも
それなりに生きていける…。
That's the kind of world
I want to protect!
How stupid!
俺が守りたいのは
そんな世の中だ！
I will not let you interfere
with my vision!
くだらぬ！
貴様らのような下賎な者どもに➡
私の理想を邪魔されてたまるか！
Like, the chakra flowing to
your tongue's been cut off...
舌に流れるチャクラを断ったし。
うぅ…。
Mission... complete!
任務… 完了だ。
Good work.
We'll be taking Gengo
and his revolutionaries
ご苦労だった。
back to the Hidden Leaf Village now.
これから
ゲンゴ および かく者たちを➡
Will you be joining us?
木ノ葉の里に連行するが→
We...
お前たちも一緒に来るか？
拙者たちは…。
You came to the rescue again.
(シカマル)また助けられちまったな…。
Sheesh...
You really are something, Naruto.
ったく…
お前は たいしたやつだぜ ナルト。
You guys!
What? Did you forget something?
(シカマル)お前ら…。
なんだ？ 忘れ物か？
Like, we were told
we're on a mission
until we get back to the village.
(鏃)里に帰るまでが任務だって
言われたし。
We shall accompany you,
Lord Shikamaru.
Huh? Oh, yeah?
(朧)シカマル殿にお供するでござるよ。
ん？ あぁ そうか。
Senpai!
Yurito?!
(ユリト)先輩！
You came too?
(シカマル)ユリト!?
I finally got to handle
a big assignment!
お前… 来てたのか。
(ユリト)俺も やっと でかい案件
任されるようになったっすよ。
O-Oh...
Huh? Senpai, aren't you being
too stiff and formal again?
(シカマル)えっ？ お… おう。
あれ～？ 先輩 また
力みすぎてるんじゃないっすか？
Clouds! The clouds!
Remember, the clouds!
雲 雲！ 雲っすよ。
Oh, yeah...
Anyways, I'm busy,
so 'scuse me!
あ… あぁ。
そんじゃ 俺 忙しいんで。
失礼しま～す。
Lord Shikamaru?
ハハハ…。
シカマル殿？
You can reach out to try
and grab the cloud...
but you can never grasp it.
雲ってのは
掴もうとしても掴めねえ。
If there's wind, it'll blow away.
Such a strange thing with no core.
風があれば 吹き飛んじまう。
芯のねえ 胡乱なもんだな。
Temari...
Huh? What is it?
Well... It's nothing important, but...
(シカマル)テマリ。
ん？ なんだ？
別に その…
なんでもねえけどよ あの…。
Um...
What is it?
Spit it out.
Go a bit easier
when you slap people, will you?
なんだ？ はっきり言え。
お前の平手打ち
ちっとは加減しろよな。
If you space out again,
I'll slap you as much as I want to!
また ボサッとしてたら
何度でも張り倒してやるぞ。
Okay... I'm counting on you for that.
じゃ… じゃあ 次も頼むぜ。
Thanks... for what you did this time.
ん？
(シカマル)今回は… ありがとな。
Is this an awkward conversation
or what?!
(いの)キィーッ！ なんつう
ぶったるい会話してんの!?
Just hurry and ask her on a date!
There, there...
デートくらい チャッチャと誘いなさいよ！
まぁ まぁ！
Ino...
Sai?
Thanks, beautiful.
(サイ)いの。
(いの)サイ？
I really felt... your kindness.
ありがとう 美人さん。
Beautiful? Oh... uh!
感じたよ キミの優しさ。
I want to thank you...
美人!? そ… そんな…。
That's if you'd let me.
何か お礼がしたいな。
キミさえよければ だけど。
Oh... Well then...
Maybe a d-date...?
だ だ… だったら あの…
デ デ デ… デートなど…。
Ino, now you're being awkward.
いの… ぶったるくなってるよ。
Maybe... next time... we can...
今度 その… なんだ…
飯でも一緒にどうだ？
go get a bite to eat.
You mean, a date?
Huh?
Are you asking me out on a date?
デートか？
はぁ!?
Well, yeah.
それは デートの誘いなのか？
ま… まぁな。
I see. A date, huh.
You don't want to?
そうか デートか。
That's not it.
嫌なのかよ？
Huh? Uh?
そうではないが…。
えっ!? ん？
Be prepared.
A date with me
can be quite a drag.
覚悟しろ。
私とのデートは面倒だぞ。
Do you have a plan?
Huh?
作戦はあるのでござろうな？
はぁ!?
Like, a date strategy.
Like I'd have one!
デートの作戦だし。
んなもん ねえよ！
Going on a first date
without a strategy
is like fighting
a Tailed Beast unarmed.
作戦なしの初デートなんて➡
素手で 尾獣と
戦うようなもんだし。
You have zero chance of winning.
勝ち目は皆無でござるな。
What would you two know?!
What are you saying?!
お前らに何がわかるんだよ!?
I do know a thing or two
about relationships.
何を隠そう 拙者 恋愛事情には
少々 うるそうござる。
You must first find out
everything you can
about Lady Temari's likes and dislikes...
まずは テマリ殿の好みを
徹底的に調べたうえで→
and come up with a careful plan.
And you need at least
three contingency plans:
入念なプランを練るでござる。
one for a sunny day,
a cloudy day and a rainy day!
それも 晴れの日 曇り 雨の
３パターンは 最低でも必要だし！
Prepare small talk
that won't bore her.
Have at least a hundred stories
in your arsenal.
相手を退屈させない小話も→
シチュエーションに応じて 100個ほど
ストックしておくべきでござろうな。
Hey, hey!
That's even more of a drag
than taking Gengo down!
おい おい…。
それって
ゲンゴを倒すより めんどくせぇ。
"Shikamaru's Story, A Cloud Drifting in the Silent Dark"
The End
kakaeta omou i tokitoshite
Sometimes, the feelings we have
kazoe kirenai itami o
Cause us immense pain
yuzurenai hokori mune ni
We've lived this entire time
imamade ikite kitadarou
With unshakeable pride in our hearts
tatakau koto de mamotte
Defending by fighting
omoigakenaku nakushite
With unexpected losses
kizutsukiai ma nande
We learn as we hurt one another
taisetsu na koto ni kizukudarou
Will we realize what's most important?
koe ga todokanai
My voice cannot reach you
soredemo (soredemo)
Even so
kokoro shinjite iyou
Let's trust our hearts
zenshin zenrei kimi wo mamoru yo
I will protect you with every essence of my being
towa ni sou towa ni
For all eternity
nankaidatte tachiagare yo
Stand up again and again
sono ishi de (sono ishi de)
By your own volition
ungai souten asu wo egaku yo
Don't give in; create a new day
tomo ni sou tomo ni
Together with friends
itsudatte akirameru
Never ever give up
na michi wo hirakou
Let's open up the path
ruru
On and on
Next Episode
The day of Naruto and Hinata's wedding draws near,
but I sent everyone out on secret missions!
It's to get them wedding presents,
but it seems it's turning out to be surprisingly difficult.
The secret behind this mission is...
something I can't talk about!
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
“Hidden Leaf Story, The Perfect Day for a Wedding, Part 1: Naruto's Wedding”
Naruto's Wedding
Tune in again!